Hey William. Guess who's coming tomorrow?
Hey William. 猜猜明天谁要来?
Who?
谁?
Mr. Bigelow.
Mr.Bigelow.
Jim Bigelow, our Chief Executive Officer?
Jim Bigelow, 我们的执行总裁?
That's right. Mr. Big.
对. 正是"老大"先生.
Why?
为什么?
He's coming in for a meeting with Anne.
来和Anne开会.
Very high level.
很高层的会议
What this organization needs is talent.
我们这个机构需要的是人才.
We need someone who will get the job done.
我们需要一个能把事情做好的人.
But we'd prefer someone presentable, with a pleasant manner.
但我们更希望是一个长相不错, 言谈举止令人愉快的人
Someone hard-working, serious, yet cheerful.
一个工作努力认真, 严谨但是欢快的人.
We want someone who can rollerblade,
我们需要一个既能溜旱冰(rollerblade),
but also likes to walk.
又喜欢步行的人.
We want... someone like that man!
我们需要……一个像他那样的人!
Yes, sir!
是的. 先生!